Speaker #1: We believe in the potential of AI to improve our
Speaker #1: lives in big and small ways.
Speaker #1: We need to make sure it's for the benefit of
Speaker #1: everyone.
Speaker #2: For the first time, we're having machines move into roles
Speaker #2: that have been the roles of human beings.
Speaker #2: Might these technologies have inadvertent effects on people in society?
Speaker #2: Do they align with people's values, their ethics?
Speaker #2: We needed to think through the implications for our company.
Speaker #1: Responsible AI is the approach that we take to developing
Speaker #1: and deploying our technology, making sure our principles are brought
Speaker #1: to life in that it empowers everyone and is inclusive
Speaker #1: and accessible for people.
Speaker #1: The job of the office of Responsible AI is to
Speaker #1: put our principles into practice by operationalising ethics across the
Speaker #1: company.
Speaker #1: The.
Speaker #2: Ether committee is responsible for deliberating about hard new questions.
Speaker #1: We are sister organisations.
Speaker #2: We have to think through what it means to detect
Speaker #2: bias, make our systems more fair, to detect errors and
Speaker #2: blind spots in our technologies, and on thinking through the
Speaker #2: kinds of advice we give to other organizations and to
Speaker #2: our leaders.
Speaker #2: Where technology can impose on privacy and human rights.
Speaker #2: Responsibility is at the core.
Speaker #2: We're learning everyday about this new role of responsible computing.
Speaker #1: We need to translate academic thought to language that our
Speaker #1: engineers and salespeople are familiar with.
Speaker #1: Our customers are grappling with many of the same issues.
Speaker #1: It's incumbent on us to share what we learn.
Speaker #2: It's about trying to do better every day, working with
Speaker #2: our customers and outside agencies to develop processes and deliver
Speaker #2: responsible computing technologies to the world.